adverbox.com 2007-06-10

# AdverBox Privacy Policy

We do not rent or sell your personal information. By personal information, we mean your name, email address, phone number, mailing address or any other personally identifiable information. We do not collect such data without your initiation, such as when you send an email to AdverBox, ask the comment system to remember you or sign up for the AdverBox Daily newsletter. 

We do place cookies on your computer. Our cookies come from our traffic counter, Google Analytics. These cookies simply let us know how many (not who) people visit the site so we have an idea of site growth.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers or advertising networks). However, AdverBox has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by AdverBox only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about users' visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about Google and cookies, contact Google.

**AdverBox Daily Newsletter**  
The AdverBox Daily Newsletter service is currently provided by FeedBurner. AdverBox has visibility on your email address and your subscription date, but ensures you that your data will be never sold or used to send unwanted emails. For any other concern about the Daily Newsletter please refer to FeedBurner.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, AdverBox may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on AdverBox.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event AdverBox goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
AdverBox contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AdverBox is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by AdverBox.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever AdverBox changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We take your privacy very seriously. If you have any concerns, please write us at open [at] adverbox [dot] com..
